I get tears every time I hear this part,
where the drums drop out and the strings
come in. Every time I hear it, I think
of this word medicinal. It feels like
healing. Like I feel like this the
feeling you get when you listen to
gospel music.
It's so good. It's so beautiful.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I went to church a whole bunch. Now I
don't like church. But then it's like I
kind of want to go to church. I kind of
I want to talk to somebody about my
faith. Like I want to talk to somebody
about my appreciation or the battles
that I feel that the universe is
throwing at me and I'm trying to make
sense of it. And sometimes with music, I
feel like I hit
a little part of like gospel that I can
[__] with.
>> Music just as an art form, as a this
thing you can't touch or see. At its
highest, at its like most powerful, it
is I think touching the divine. You
capture whatever that thing is.
>> Yeah.
The intangible.
And like a moment like this,
congratulations cuz it's really good.
>> is a really crazy compliment.
>> [music]